Hey folks, how are you doing? This is another jumpsuit up video. It's episode 10.
We remember back to episode 2 there was a PVC catsuit and now we have another PVC catsuit for this episode.
This is a catsuit by the company called Vaughan & Boone. They're UK based and they told me that I'm the first person to present their catsuit on YouTube.
yay thanks a lot for trusting in me this is the vortex catsuit they call it
themselves their masterpiece because the cut is really cool with multiple panels
and the specialty here is that they offer it in two length sizes so to say
or they call it body loops problem I have often is that a catsuit is too
short in my body length here and this one should solve the problem because
this is the tall body loop length. The material is a super soft four-way
stretch PVC so I hope I'm going to get into this really fast and really good. Let's find out!
Thank you.
That was really quick, it was super easy to put on and I have to say it's super comfortable
because I don't know, it's long enough, there's no tension here at the neck, it's wide enough
here at the neck, the arms are long enough, the legs are long enough, so really love this
one and I have to agree with Charlotte the owner of Worn and Boom because she wrote me a letter
thanks for that and also for the Christmas card. She says that in my experience body loop is the
most important measurement for catsuit design and the body loop is the length here and I totally
agree if it's not long enough then it's uncomfortable and here it's super comfy.
And with the tall fitting it's also great for cross dresses because usually
men have longer upper body and the problem is solved here so you can check
out their homepage they have a cross-dressing section there and of
course I'll link everything down below. There was not only a catsuit in the
parcel but also a corset.
I love how thin this is and how well it goes together with the catsuit so this is really
a great combination and the catsuit itself fits really good in the lower part.
In the upper part it could be a bit tighter but with the corset it works out pretty well.
And what I like to do, I normally take my cloth I'm using to shine up my latex and rub it over the PVC.
And the PVC gets even more shinier as well.
This way.
Since this is a rather plain look, I'm going to do a second look with a few buckles.
So I'm going to change my shoes, add a belt and we'll see how that works out.
Alright, that's the look with the metal accessories, the shoes, the belt and the choker.
I really like this belt over corset look here.
But what do you think?
Which version do you prefer?
Leave a comment below and by the way don't forget to subscribe to my channel.
I'm really happy with this catsuit.
I have to say it again, it's really comfortable.
So I'm going to enjoy this one.
Have a nice evening, see you around, bye!